United University Professions (UUP); Records apap039
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of the Secretary, 1968-1999; IV; 61.73 cubic ft.
  - Chapters, 1968-1996; 3; 17.0 cubic ft.
    - Chapter Files [RESTRICTED], 1968-1996; 3.3; 14.66 cubic ft.
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], January 1988-June 1989 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], October 1989-February 1990 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], March 1990-December 1992 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Upstate Medical Center (Syracuse)-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], April 1978-October 1978; December 1980-Fall 1983 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], September 1975-November 1977 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], November 1978-May 1982 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], June 1982-May 1988 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], November 1988-April 1991; September 1992-May 1993 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - Utica/Rome-Newsletter [RESTRICTED], February 1980-November 1987 (Box IV.3.3.14 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - Albany [RESTRICTED], September 1993-February 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Alfred [RESTRICTED], October 1993-March 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Binghamton [RESTRICTED], June 1993-December 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Brockport [RESTRICTED], October 1993-May 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Brooklyn Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], June 1993-August 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Brooklyn Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], August 1994-October 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Brooklyn Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], November 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - SUNY Buffalo [RESTRICTED], July 1993-November 1993 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - SUNY Buffalo [RESTRICTED], December 1993-December 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - SUNY Buffalo [RESTRICTED], May 1996-July 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], June 1993-April 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], May 1994-December 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], December 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - Buffalo State University College [RESTRICTED], August 1993-April 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - Canton [RESTRICTED], June 1993-July 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
      - Cobleskill [RESTRICTED], June 1993-February 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
      - Cortland [RESTRICTED], June 1993-March 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
      - Delhi [RESTRICTED], March 1994; February 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
      - Empire State College [RESTRICTED], February 1994-July 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
      - Environmental Science and Forestry [RESTRICTED], February 1995-March 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
      - Farmingdale [RESTRICTED], June 1993-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
      - Fredonia [RESTRICTED], June 1993-March 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
      - Geneseo [RESTRICTED], February 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
      - Maritime [RESTRICTED], October 1993-February 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
      - Morrisville [RESTRICTED], December 1993-December 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
      - New Paltz [RESTRICTED], October 1993-August 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
      - New York State Theater Institute [RESTRICTED], November 1993-June 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
      - Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], March 1994-May 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
      - Oneonta [RESTRICTED], February 1995-July 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
      - Optometry, College of [RESTRICTED], June 1993-June 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], June 1993-February 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
      - Oswego [RESTRICTED], March 1994-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
      - Oswego Election Challenge [RESTRICTED], December 1993-March 1994 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], June 1993-November 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - Potsdam [RESTRICTED], June 1993-May 1996 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - Purchase [RESTRICTED], January 1994-February 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
      - Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], July 1993-November 1995 (Box IV.3.3.15 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], July 1993-June 1994 (Box IV.3.3.16 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], July 1994-August 1994 (Box IV.3.3.16 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Stony Brook Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], August 1994-August 1995 (Box IV.3.3.16 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], June 1993-December 1994 (Box IV.3.3.16 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Syracuse Health Science Center [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box IV.3.3.16 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], February 1995 (Box IV.3.3.16 (3.3-Chapter Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Committees, Task Forces, and Working Groups [RESTRICTED], 1978 February-1993 May; 4; 12.0 cubic ft.
    The records in this series document, to varying degrees, the activities of UUP's standing committees, ad hoc committees, joint labor-management committees, task forces, and working groups. Included for most committees are the administrative correspondence created at UUP's administrative office setting up meetings, obtaining approval from the Governor's Office of Employee Relations for organizational leave time for meeting attendees, and confirming committee appointments. Lists of committee members are also frequently included.
    The substantive work of each committee is documented by meeting agendas and minutes; the materials, such as third-party reports, distributed to committee members for their use in preparing for committee meetings; correspondence between UUP's President and the committee chairperson; and correspondence from UUP's officers and the committee chairperson to the committee as a whole. The records for joint labor-management committees include reports and correspondence prepared by the state with regard to the committee, as well as communications between only UUP's participants on those committees. If a formal report was at some point prepared by a committee or task force, drafts of the report are often included in that committee's or task force's records. Finally, the reports made by the committee chairperson to Delegate Assemblies are occasionally included in this series. (Committee chairperson reports are also found in the Delegate Assembly records in Series 2 of this Subgroup.)
    As of February 2001, UUP's standing committees are: Retired Membership, Affirmative Action, Elections and Credentials, Finance, Grievance, Legislation, Membership, Negotiations, Part-Time Concerns, Solidarity, and Women's Rights and Concerns. Over the years, UUP's ad hoc committees, task forces, and working groups have addressed a variety of issues, particularly in the area of higher education and improving SUNY (for example, the Student Retention and Recruitment Committee, the Public Education Committee, the Undergraduate Education Task Force, the Teacher Education Task Force, the University Development Committee, and the Excellence Committee). Issues of concern to particular segments of UUP's bargaining unit have also been addressed (for example, the Colleges of Technology Task Force, the Health Science Center Concerns Committee, and the Nursing Profession Work Group). Joint labor-management committees have addressed safety and health issues, child care, health benefits, professional study leaves, employee assistance programs, salary disparities, and providing retraining and re-education opportunities for retrenched employees. Finally, some of UUP's committees have focused on improving UUP and its operations such as the Constitutional Study Committee, the Computer Technology Committee, and the Re-Imagine UUP Committee.
    Committee-specific materials include election result reports and correspondence on possible election irregularities for the Elections and Credentials Committee; financial summaries and the report of the treasurer, and chapter budget requests and approval requests for extraordinary expenditures for the Finance Committee; chapter responses to a survey on membership and membership recruitment activities in 1982 for the Membership Committee; proposed legislation and state budgets for the Legislation Committee; and studies on indoor air pollution and other workplace health concerns for the Safety and Health Committee. There is some overlap between the records of the Membership Committee and Retired Membership Committee because correspondence were occasionally addressed to both groups, and they deal with an overlapping area of interest. The files for the Negotiations Committee has correspondence, appointment letters, and meeting information for UUP's Negotiations Team and its Ad Hoc Advisory Committee for Negotiations, occasional negotiations bulletins and responses to members on issues of concern for negotiations, and multiple copies of lists of committee and team members as well as some attendance lists for negotiations meetings and workshops. Grievance committee records include reports to the president recommending the continued pursuit or the abandonment of specific grievances. Background materials for some of the applications submitted to the Legal Defense Fund Committee are included with the records of that committee.
    The amount of materials available for each committee, task force, and working group, and the degree of organization of those materials, varies. The records that make up this series were primarily taken from the main committee records maintained by UUP's statewide secretary. Frequently, however, additional folders for specific committees were encountered during processing and incorporated into this series. Except in a few instances when the additional materials were retained separately because the identity of the individual maintaining the records was known, the new materials were interfiled in chronological order into the main committee files, which were themselves organized, to the extent possible, into chronological order during processing. The records for the Legislation Committee during the 1980s were in particular disarray and it was only possible to put them in rough chronological order. Throughout this series, undated materials were kept near their original location but due to the sometimes widely varying dates of the documents found on either side of undated documents, some undated materials may not be correctly located by date. The names of a few committees and task forces have changed over the years, however for the most part just one name is used for each committee in the folder list for this series.
    Materials related to committee work during the mid-1970s can also be found in the SPA/UUP Administrative Office General Files in Series 2 of Subgroup II, usually under the name of the topic that each committee dealt with rather than the committee name itself (i.e., Legislation or Membership rather than Legislation Committee or Membership Committee). Committee files for 1975-1981 are also located in Subgroup III, Subseries 3.1, Wakshull Administration, Subject Files. Finally, the project and subject files in Series 5 of Subgroup III include materials relating to the work of some committees, task forces, and working groups during the Reilly presidency from May 1987 to May 1993.
    - Academic Research and Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1990 September-1993 April (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1981 May (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1981 June-1982 March (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982 April-1983 November (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1983 December-1985 October (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 November-1986 December 05 (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 December 08-1987 March (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 April-1987 July (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1989 May (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 June-1992 December (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action Joint Labor/Management Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 August-1989 March (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 11)
    - Affirmative Action Committee (Joint Labor/Management) minutes and leave grant applications [RESTRICTED], 85-88 contract; 3 folders (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12-14)
    - Affirmative Action Committee-Cultural Diversity Steering Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 June (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 15)
    - AIDS Work Group reference materials [RESTRICTED], 1986-1989 (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - AIDS Work Group [RESTRICTED], 1987 December-1989 January (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Archives Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1991 May (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Career Development Committee (Joint Labor-Management/Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Employees) [RESTRICTED], 1979 July-1980 May (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19)
    - Career Development Committee (Joint Labor-Management/Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Employees) [RESTRICTED], 1980 September-1982 March (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 20)
    - Chapter Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1988 February; 1990 March-1991 September; 1992 November-1993 April (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 21)
    - Chapter Release Time (Article 11.6) Subcommittee (Chapter Development Committee) [RESTRICTED], 1985 December-1991 March (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 22)
    - Child Care Advisory Committee, New York State Labor/Management [RESTRICTED], 1987 November-1993 April (Box IV.4.1 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Clinical Practice Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1986 July-1987 January (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Clinical Practice Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1987 February-1988 March (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - Clinical Practice Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1990 October (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women, Committee on [RESTRICTED], 1981 July-1982 September (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Colleges of Technology, Task Force on [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1993 May (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Computer Technology Committee (T. Matthews, Treasurer, file) [RESTRICTED], 1984 July-1988 June (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Computer Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1985 September (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - Computer Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 October-1989 June (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - Computer Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1993 March (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - Constitutional Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1979 February (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10)
    - Constitution Study Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 August-1988 December (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 11)
    - Constitutional Study Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 January-1990 February (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12)
    - Constitutional Study Committee [RESTRICTED], 1990 March-1991 August (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 13)
    - Constitutional Study Committee [RESTRICTED], 1991 September-1993 April (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 14)
    - Continuity of Employment Committee (established by 1982-85 Contract) [RESTRICTED], 1983 February-1983 August (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 15)
    - Continuity of Employment Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1983 October-1984 February (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - Continuity of Employment Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1984 April-1984 September (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Continuity of Employment Committee-Academic Recall Study by Peat Marwick [RESTRICTED], 1986 April-1986 June (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Continuity of Employment Committee-Academic Recall Study by Peat Marwick [RESTRICTED], 1986 July-1986 September (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19)
    - Disparity Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982 December-1983 November (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 20)
    - Disparity Committee [RESTRICTED], 1983 November-1984 September; 1985 April (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 21)
    - Disparity Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1989 October (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 22)
    - Education Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 June-1989 December (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Education Technology Committee [RESTRICTED], 1990 January-1990 September; 1991 September-1992 January (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 24)
    - Educational Opportunity Centers (EOC) Concerns Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 April-1993 March (Box IV.4.2 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 25)
    - Educational Opportunity Centers (EOC) Concerns Committee (T. Corigliano, VP for Professionals file) [RESTRICTED], 1987 December-1990 August (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Educational Opportunity Centers (EOC) Concerns Committee (T. Corigliano, VP for Professionals file) [RESTRICTED], 1991 June-1992 March (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - EOC Concerns Committee (W. Scheuerman, VP for Academics file) [RESTRICTED], 1990 June-1992 January (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - EOC Concerns Committee (W. Scheuerman, VP for Academics file) [RESTRICTED], 1992 February-1993 May (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1981 May (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1981 July 31-1983 November 08 (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1983 November 10-1985 August (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 7)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 September-1987 April 03 (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 8)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 April 03-1987 September 22 (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 9)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 September 24-1988 July (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 10)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 August-1989 May (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 11)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 June-1993 May (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 12)
    - Employment Committee (Joint Labor/Management) [RESTRICTED], 1988 September-1989 January (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 13)
    - Employment Committee (Joint Labor/Management) [RESTRICTED], 1989 February-1989 June (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 14)
    - Employment Committee (Joint Labor/Management) [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1993 May (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 15)
    - Employment Committee-Professional Evaluation Survey [RESTRICTED], 1989 October (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 16)
    - Evaluate Full-Time Secretarial Assistance, Subcommittee to [RESTRICTED], 1990 October-1991 January (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 17)
    - Excellence Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1989 January-1989 December 12 (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 18)
    - Excellence Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1989 December 14-1990 October (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 19)
    - Excellence Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1990 October-1991 August (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 20)
    - Excellence Committee (Joint Labor-Management) 1991 Excellence Award Nominees Round 2 [RESTRICTED], 2 folders (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 21-22)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act Committee (Joint Labor-Management) [RESTRICTED], 1986 April-1987 April (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 23)
    - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1979 April (Box IV.4.3 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 24)
    - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1979 August-1981 June (Box IV.4.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1981 July 31-1982 July (Box IV.4.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982 August-1984 May (Box IV.4.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1984 August-1985 August (Box IV.4.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 September-1986 August (Box IV.4.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 5)
    - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1987 September 30 (Box IV.4.4 (IV-Office of the Secretary), Folder 6)